# 血滴子
# 注：参考邵氏电影《血滴子》的官方英文名
The Flying Guillotine
# 给大家介绍下使用血滴子的姿势和步法
Let me introduce the posture and footwork of the Flying Guillotine
# 首先把血滴子提高到头部
First lift the Flying Guillotine to the head
# 方便于瞄准
which eases aiming
# 眼睛凝视目标
Stare at the target
# 左手攥住锁链放置腰部的后上方
Hold the chain with your left hand and place it above your lower back
# 这样容易控制锁链的长度
So it's easy to control the length of the chain
# 也不影响血滴子的旋转轨迹
And it does not affect the rotation of the Flying Guillotine
# 它所使用的步伐是阴阳两合步
The footwork is called Yin and Yang Biharmony
# 像这样小腿自然弯曲
Like this, the knee bends naturally
# 因为这样能够让身体自然的倾向目标
Because this can make the body naturally lean to the target
# 减少身体受到攻击的面积
And reduce the area of the body under attack
# 也方便身体左右的移动
It is also convenient for the body to move left and right
# 给大家完整地演示一下
Let me give you a complete demonstration
# 自行车电风扇
Bicycle Fan
# 自行车一直是我们绿色出行的首选交通工具
Bicycles have always been our first choice for environment friendly traveling
# 但是夏天骑的时候会非常热
But in summer, it’s very hot when riding
# 所以说我做了一个自行车电风扇
So I made a bicycle fan
# 安装也非常方便
Installation is also very convenient
# 下面我给大家演示一下
Let me show you
# 首先把自行车的车筐取下
First, remove the bicycle basket
# 然后把这个电风扇安装上去就可以了
Then just install the fan
# 这就是安装好的样子
This is how it looks like after installation
# 只要轻轻一推 他就会快速地转动
Just a light push, the fan will spin quickly
# 像这样骑起来就会有风
Ride like this, there will be wind
# 比较凉快
Very cool
# 如果你觉得我的发明不错的话，麻烦红心点点
If you think my invention is good, then please like and subscribe
# 谢谢
Thank you
# 西瓜接汁器
Watermelon Juice Collector
# 夏天 大家都比较喜欢吃西瓜
In summer, everyone likes to eat watermelon
# 但是吃的过程中 你会发现
However, while eating, you will find out that
# 西瓜汁流得满手都是
Watermelon juice flows all over the hands
# 而且会滴在地板上
And it drops on the floor
# 然后说还得清理
Then you have to clean it up
# 非常麻烦
Very troublesome
# 现在解决办法一般都是
The current solution is generally
# 找一个垃圾桶接着
Find a trash can to collect the watermelon juice
# 这么看着吃相不是特别美观
So the eating manner may not look very good
# 而且家里来客人的时候
And when guests come
# 你不一定家里有这么多的垃圾桶
There may not be so many trash cans at home
# 所以说我做了一个
So I made a
# 西瓜接汁器
Watermelon juice collector
# 这就是那个西瓜接汁器
This is the Watermelon juice collector
# 这里有两个小尖刺
There are two spikes here
# 是用于固定西瓜用的
Which are used to fix the watermelon
# 把切好的西瓜
Put the sliced watermelon in
# 然后这里是供吐籽用的
You can spit the watermelon seeds here
# 有了这个西瓜接汁器
With this watermelon juice collector
# 你就可以摆脱垃圾桶的束缚
You are free from the trash can
# 在家里随时随地高雅地吃西瓜
And can enjoy watermelon anytime and anywhere at home
# 西瓜网球拍
Watermelon tennis racket
# 做了个西瓜网球拍
I made this watermelon tennis racket
# 给您录一个
Let me record it for you
# 压水井
Manual Well Pump
# 用过的都老了吧
People who have used it have become old, right?
# 感谢收看 欢迎订阅 —— 手工耿
Thanks for watching and welcome to subscribe -- Handy Geng